in this lecture and the next one we will
在这节课和下一节课中，我们将
make a 3D text effect on a Sunburst
在日出上制作3D文本效果
background
背景
we will start by making the Sunburst
我们将从制作《日出》开始
background using radial gradients I
使用径向渐变的背景I
right click on the canvas and choose
在画布上右键单击并选择
document properties I set the canvas to
我将画布设置为的文档属性
landscape
景观
I activate snapping
我激活了捕捉
I click on the rectangle tool I drag
我点击我拖动的矩形工具
over the canvas where it will snap now
在画布上，它将在哪里折断
let's create a radial gradient I click
让我们创建一个径向渐变，我单击
on the fill and stroke tab I click on
在填充和描边选项卡上，我点击
radial gradient for the inside color I
内色的径向渐变
pick an orange
摘一个橙子
and for the outer color I will select
至于外色，我会选择
red I want to bring the outer color more
红色的，我想多带点外色。
to Orange
致橙色
to go from red to orange I will drag the
要从红色变为橙色，我将拖动
Hue to the right you can also drag on
向右的色调您也可以拖动
the outer ring of the color wheel and
色轮的外环和
for fine tuning you can click on the
对于微调，您可以点击
plus and minus icons I can't see the
加上和减去图标我看不到
inner gradient color very well so I will
内渐变颜色很好，所以我会
drag its Hue more to Orange I also want
拖动它的色调到橙色我也想要
the color to be a bit lighter to do this
颜色要浅一点才能做到这一点
I drag the lightness by dragging the
我通过拖拽
endpoints I can change the dimensions of
我可以更改端点的尺寸
the radial gradient now that we have our
径向渐变现在我们有了
gradient let's create the Sunburst I
渐变，让我们来创作《日出I》
click on the star polygon tool like the
单击星形多边形工具，如
rectangle and ellipse tool the start
矩形和椭圆工具的起点
tool is a live shape I can make spikes
工具是一个活生生的形状，我可以做出钉子
longer and shorter
越长越短
and I can increase or decrease the
我可以增加或减少
amount of spikes to get a triangle I
得到一个三角形的尖峰数量i
need three corners and I need the spoke
我需要三个角，我需要轮辐
ratio to be 0.5 I drag then press Ctrl
比率为0.5我拖动，然后按Ctrl键
and rotate until the triangle points
然后旋转，直到三角形指向
down
降下来
to use a path effect it is best to use a
若要使用路径效果，最好使用
regular path
规则路径
to turn a live shape to a regular path I
要将活动形状转换为常规路径，请执行以下操作
go to path object to path now I hold
转到路径对象到路径现在我按住
shift and drag the side in I drag the
按住Shift键并将边拖入I拖动
triangle to the center until I see cusp
三角形到中心，直到我看到尖点
node to object midpoint
节点到对象中点
now I want to copy and rotate the
现在我想复制和旋转
triangle
三角形
I click on pathfx from the menu I choose
我从我选择的菜单中点击pathfx
rotate copies I click on the Node tool I
旋转副本我单击节点工具I
drag the rotation origin point to the
将旋转原点拖动到
midpoint where it will snap I want the
它将折断的中点我想要
beams to be larger so I drag over the
梁更大，所以我把它拖到
points I select show transformation
我选择的点显示变换
handles for selected nodes I scale the
选定节点的句柄I缩放
beam until all beams are outside the
梁，直到所有梁都在
rectangle I set number of copies to 28 I
矩形I将副本数设置为28 I
hold shift and drag aside to adjust the
按住Shift键并将鼠标拖到一边可调整
width of the beams I don't want black
光束的宽度，我不想要黑色的
but white transparent beams so I click
但是白色透明的光束，所以我点击
on the white Swatch then I go to my
在白色的斯沃琪上，然后我走到我的
layers to set the opacity
用于设置不透明度的层
I set opacity to 50 to get a better
我将不透明度设置为50以获得更好的
blending with a gradient I set the blend
使用渐变混合我设置了混合
mode to soft light
模式到柔和灯光
now I want to hide the beams that go
现在我想隐藏那些消失的光束
outside the gradient I right click on
在渐变之外，我右击
the gradient and choose set clip group I
渐变，然后选择设置剪贴组I
drag the Sunburst above the clip folder
将SunBurst拖动到剪辑文件夹上方
I name the path beams and I name the
我将路径命名为Beans，并将
rectangle gradient now I want to place
现在我要放置矩形渐变
some sunlight at the top
顶上有一些阳光
I click on the ellipse tool and drag an
我单击椭圆工具并拖动一个
ellipse
椭圆
I click on yellow I set blur to 50 I
我点击黄色，我将模糊设置为50 i
drag the yellow inside the clip group
将黄色拖动到剪辑组内部
and place it below the beams I hold
把它放在我手中的横梁下面
shift and drag the side so that the
按住Shift键并拖动边框，以便
yellow covers the top of the Sunburst I
黄色盖住了日出I的顶部
drag the top and bottom handles to place
拖动顶部和底部手柄以放置
the sunlight I name the shape sunlight
阳光我把这个形状命名为阳光
and the layer Sunburst in the next
和下一层的阳光
lecture we will create the 3D text
我们将创建3D文本